(Penny:)- So do you like Stuart?
- I don't know.
(Amy:)He's nice. He's funny.
He has the sallow-drawn countenance...
(Amy:)...associated with an overactive
thyroid gland. That's kind of hot.
(Penny:)Look, sweetie, we all love Sheldon, but
you've been with him over a year now.
(Penny:)If it's not going anywhere,
what does it hurt to look around?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, I guess they're not engaged
Iike me and Howie.
(Penny:)For what it's worth, engaged people can
Iook around too. Lot of options out there.
(Sheldon:)Where's Stuart?
(Raj:)Out.
- Who are you?
- I'm Dale. He left me in charge.
(Bernadette:)- Really?
- Yeah.
(Dale:)I don't get it either.
I wanna return this Wild West
and Witches Ka'a expansion pack.